

# MARTIN KAPRÁL

# FRONTEND DEVELOPER

I am a 27-year-old developer from Slovakia based in Brno, Czechia. I enjoy finding creative solutions and focusing on details. I am dedicated to designing experiences that are user-friendly, accessible, and tailored to meet the needs of the users.

PORTFOLIO LINK:

https://martinkapral.netlify.app

# +421 949 784 222 martin.kapraal@gmail.com

#### **HARD SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React JS
- React Router
- Tailwind
- GitHub
- FireBase
- Framer-Motion
- VSCode
- Netlify
- Figma

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Creativity
- Attention to detail
- Communication
- Teamwork
- · Continuous learning
- Adaptability
- Critical thinking
- Positive attitude

#### **HOBBIES**

When I'm not coding, you can find me playing my synths in my home studio, exercising in the gym or exploring nature on my bicycle.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **PROJECT COORDINATOR** AT TROAX SK S.R.O.

PART-TIME January 2018 - June 2021

- Performed installation tasks as required
- Ensured the transportation and assembly process
- Reported on the project schedule progress

#### SALES AND INSTALLATION MANAGER AT TROAX SK S.R.O.

FULL-TIME June 2021 - March 2024

- Led and managed tasks from planning and installation to the finished project
- Communicated with material suppliers and external project managers
- Introduced the company's products and services to new customers
- Monitored and secured warehouse supplies and capacities
- Defined clear goals and objectives

# OTHER EXPERIENCE

**WORK AND TRAVEL** IN BRECKENRIDGE, COLORADO June 2019 - September 2019

### EDUCATION

## **BACHELOR'S DEGREE, MASS MEDIA COMMUNICATION**

UNIVERSITY OF SS. CYRIL AND METHODIUS, TRNAVA September 2018 - June 2021

# LANGUAGES

**SLOVAK** 

**ENGLISH** 

Native speaker

B2

#### COURSES

THE FRONTEND DEVELOPER PATH AT SCRIMBA

November 2023 - May 2024